callupcontact.com 2016-02-02

# Callupcontact Privacy Policy

We use cookies to provide services to you. By continuing to use this website, we assume that you agree to our use of cookies.     [](http://www.callupcontact.com/documents/cookie.php)

For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 we confirm that the proprietor and operator of the CALLUPCONTACT Website at [www.callupcontact.com](http://www.callupcontact.com/) (the “Website”) is Y1000 LTD (“CALLUPCONTACT”, “We” or “Us”); a company registered in England with company number 08762251 whose registered address is at 78 York Street London W1H 1DP, United Kingdom. 

CALLUPCONTACT and its affiliate entities take your privacy very seriously. We ask that you read this Privacy Policy carefully as it contains important information about what to expect when CALLUPCONTACT collects personal information about you and how CALLUPCONTACT manages your personal information. 

The Privacy Policy addresses the treatment of personal information that CALLUPCONTACT receives, collects, stores and utilises in order to provide its services, and may be subject to change without notice to accommodate new services, functions or other updates of the website.  

By using the Service, visiting the Website, contacting Us through the Website, submitting your personal information, creating an account you consent to the use of that information as set out in this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions. 

**1.   PERSONAL AND NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION **

“User” or “You” means anyone who visits the Website or any of its pages, registers on the Website and uses the Service. 

“Generic Information” means IP address, referring sites, visited pages, internet browser, language, geographical location, date and time which is automatically recorded when anyone visits any of this Website’s web pages.   
“Personal Information” means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, without limitation, name and surname, address, telephone number and email address (“Information”). You can browse our Website without revealing any personal Information about Yourself. 

“Service information” means information that may be recorded, stored and retrieved by the service Callupcontact.com provides. This service includes recording, storing and retrieval of the user’s contact details. In providing this service, contact details of the User are recorded, stored and retrieved. Dependant on specific service requests, such information may include name, contact information, financial and billing information, product and service preferences, personal demographic and personal interest information of users. 

“Feedback Information” means information that may be recorded, collected and retrieved by this website when a User provides feedback on errors, security, compliments, suggestions, complaints or requests assistance. 

“Communication correspondence” means information passed via email, phone or other communication method which may be recorded, stored and retrieved when anyone contacts CALLUPCONTACT. 

**2\. THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU**  

When You register for an account with Us (“User Account”) You provide Us with some of Your Personal Information such as Your name, surname, business name, country of residence and e-mail address.

While using the Service We automatically record information from Your device and its software as well as Your activity using the Service, including, but with no limitation to, Your Device Internet Protocol address (hereinafter referred to as “IP address”), browser type, the Web page visited before You were redirected or came to the Website, information You search for on the Website, identification numbers associated with Your device(s), browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views, Website navigation, Your locale preferences, system configuration information, Your mobile carrier and other interactions with the Service.

**3\. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION ABOUT YOU**

We  gather the Information outlined above to allow Us to create Your User Account, for You to manage the details of your business profile, to assess the validity and Your connection with a business profile where a removal request, update or privacy request that You submit on the “Request a Change” link on each business profile, communicate with You on any matter related to Your User Account and the provision of the Service. We may also retain Your Information in order for you to change your business details in the future and for Us to contact You about other products and services We think may be of interest to You. 

We may also use aggregate information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring the Website usage in order to help Us to develop the Website and Our services. We may also provide such aggregate Information to third parties. These statistics will not include Information that can be used to identify You. 

From time to time We may provide Your Information to our customer service agencies for research and analysis purposes so that We can monitor and improve the Service We provide.  This Information will not include any information You might be identified by. We, Our agents and sub-contractors may also contact You by post, email or telephone to ask You for Your feedback and comments on Our services. 

We will disclose Information about You only when the disclosure is required or authorised by law or by this Privacy Policy. 

CALLUPCONTACT shall use contractual or other means to provide a comparable level of protection while the Information is being processed by a third party. 

We will not be responsible for the information You might accidentally place in the public view on the Website, the business information that previously belonged to your business and is now personal information, such as, but not limited to phone number, physical address or e-mail address. 

**4\. HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION**

CALLUPCONTACT continuously aims and continuously reviews methods to improve its security to safeguard User’s stored Information. 

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of Your Personal Information. We will store all the Personal Information You provide on our secure (password-and firewall-protected) servers. We also have put in place security procedures as well as technical and organisational measures to safeguard Your Personal Information. When you enter Information such as credit card details, We encrypt the transmission of that Information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard Your Personal Information. However, You should be aware that the use of the Internet is not entirely secure and for this reason We cannot guarantee the security or integrity of any Personal Information which is transferred from You or to You via the Internet. 

You are solely responsible for keeping Your password and other login details confidential. We will not ask You for Your password (except when You log in to the Website). 

Generic information, Service Information, Feedback Information and Communication correspondence could be viewed or used by CALLUPCONTACT, restricted to staff, developers, contractors or agents in the employment of CALLUPCONTACT: (a) to provide and improve the service of the website; (b) to maintain and strengthen security through logging usage; (c) to analyse, research and audit statistical usage of the website; (d) to support and provide help in usage of the website by registered members; (e) to maintain and further develop the Website. 

**5\. OVERSEAS TRANSFERS**

  Due to the global nature of the Internet the Information You provide may be transferred to countries within the European Economic Area (‘EEA’). By submitting Your Information You consent to these transfers for the purposes specified above.

**6\. ACCESSING, UPDATING AND DELETING YOUR INFORMATION**  
You warrant that the Information which You are required to provide when You register with Us is true, accurate, current and complete in all respects. You agree not to impersonate any other person, whether legal or natural or to use a fictitious name or a name that You have no authorisation to use. We want to ensure that Your Personal Information is accurate and up to date. If any of the Information that You have provided to Us changes or if You wish to cancel Your User Account, please let Us know the correct details by logging in and changing the details in the settings area. On each business profile page there is a ‘Request a Change’ link to update business information  You may ask Us, or We may ask You, to correct Information You or We believe might be inaccurate, and You may also ask Us to remove Information which is inaccurate using the ‘Request to Change’ link.   
You may exercise Your rights of access, request of correction, erasure and objection or revoke Your consent for receipt of commercial communications by sending an email by logging in and changing the details in the settings area or you can contact us at  privacy@callupcontact.com 

You have the right to request a copy of the Information that We hold about You. If You would like a copy of some or all of your Personal Information, please send an email to privacy@callupcontact.com.  We may charge You up to £10  for a subject access request (the “Fee”). Where the Fee is requested, We may not comply with Your request until We have received the Fee. The maximum Fee We can charge is £10 . If We ask for the Fee and do not receive it, We might send You a reminder. CALLUPCONTACT retains the right to decline processing a request to retrieve archived Information for any User where such service may interfere with operational performance, security issues and the privacy of other Users or organisations using the Service. 

By deleting or altering information through the usage of the Service provided by CALLUPCONTACT, the information may be lost or altered in such manner that is beyond the control of CALLUPCONTACT and CALLUPCONTACT shall bear no liability for any such lost or altered information. 

**7\. USAGE OF INFORMATION BY USERS**

When a User registers to make use of further services provided by CALLUPCONTACT the User is provided with protected access to a User Account, which contains Personal Information that only that User can record, store and retrieve. Through the use of the Website, Users may elect to publish or send in part or in whole Personal Information to the public. The public’s subsequent usage of that Personal Information then becomes a matter of prior consent and falls outside the scope of this Privacy Policy. Users are encouraged to review settings on social media facilities with which they interact to ensure they understand what information may be collected, used and commonly publicly shared. 

**8\. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

CALLUPCONTACT, its staff, developers, contractors or others in the employment or hired by CALLUPCONTACT will under no circumstances sell, rent or lease any of Your Personal Information to third parties. 

Staff, developers, contractors or others in the employment or hired by CALLUPCONTACT at times may assist Users in the use of the Website. In so doing CALLUPCONTACT or its staff, developers, contractors or others in the employment or hired by CALLUPCONTACT do not disclose any Information to parties who have not been granted access via their User Account and only disclose information related directly to the inquiring User. CALLUPCONTACT may provide third parties with Information pertaining to a User, subject to CALLUPCONTACT’s having obtained prior permission, with appropriate notice, from the specific User, unless in circumstances where CALLUPCONTACT is required to satisfy an applicable law, regulation or legal process, to prevent, detect or otherwise address fraud, security and technical issues, in order to protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of CALLUPCONTACT, its Users or the public as required or permitted by law.

**9.   LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES **

There may be links on the Website to websites and webpages outside the ownership and control of CALLUPCONTACT (“Third Party Websites”). CALLUPCONTACT does not endorse nor make any representations regarding Third Party Websites and encourages anyone who makes use of such websites to read the privacy policy of those Third Party Websites. By using those links You are leaving the domain of the CALLUPCONTACT Website and its Privacy Policy set out therein, and entering Third Party Websites and areas of the Internet where CALLUPCONTACT, its staff, developers, contractors or others hired by or in its employment cannot be reasonably held responsible for the privacy of Your Information. 

**10\. CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**

CALLUPCONTACT does not purport to substitute for parental control and does not knowingly collect Information from minor children nor does it target the Website to children of minor age. 

**11\. SALE OF BUSINESS**

If CALLUPCONTACT’s business is sold or integrated with another business Your Information may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers and will be passed onto the new owners of the business.

**12\. MODIFICATIONS TO PRIVACY POLICY**

We keep the Privacy Policy under regular review. If We amend Our Privacy Policy the relevant modified version will be posted on this page. We may also place notices on other pages of the Website so that you may become aware of the Privacy Policy modification. This Privacy Policy was last updated on 16 July 2014. 

**13\. SUGGESTIONS**

CALLUPCONTACT regularly reviews, educates, monitors and requires it staff, developers, contractors or agents in the employment of or hired by CALLUPCONTACT to respect the privacy of others by practicing the terms contained in this Privacy Policy. Feel free to direct any concerns or questions regarding any of our privacy policies or practices via privacy@callupcontact.com   Our recommended contact method is a “Request a Change” link available on each business profile which provides You with a ticket to track your request. CALLUPCONTACT is committed to resolve privacy matter complaints and will submit to any relevant authorised forum in order to do so in circumstances where the User and CALLUPCONTACT cannot resolve such matter themselves.
